A Guide to the Wena Dows Architectural Collection, 1952-2005
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Wena Dows Architectural Collection, 1952-2005
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1990-013
21.1 cu. ft. 1 box; 86 oversize folders
Architect Wena Dows earned her B.A. in Architecture from the University of California, Berkeley, in 1950 and began working independently, specializing in residential remodeling, in 1954. Along with her architectural commitments she also worked as a nutritionist. The Wena Dows Architectural Collection contains drawings, supporting text documents, photographs and slides of Dows' addition and renovation projects for residences in California from 1952 to 2005, along with information about a few commercial projects.
Dows, Wena W., 1928-
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
The creator donated the Wena Dows material to the International Archive of Women in Architecture in May 1990. An addition to the collection was received in 2009.
Biographical Information
Wena Dows was born in 1928, in Taft, California. She completed a BA in Architecture from the University of California, Berkeley, in 1950. From 1950 till 1954 she worked as a draftsperson for Ernest F. Winkler, AIA, in San Francisco and for Clyde Bentley, a consulting engineer in Oakland, California. In 1954 she started working independently, specializing in residential architecture. She mostly undertook addition and renovation work to residences in California.
Dows also took courses in nutrition at UCLA, Los Angeles City College, American Institute of Family Relations. Along with her architectural commitments she also worked as a nutritionist. In 1968, Wena Dows was a Diet Analyst for the Retail Clerks Union. She started teaching healthy cooking in 1969 and taught at Venice Adult School, Los Angeles School District for many years. Later she started "The Healthy Gourmet" classes from her residence.
Wena Dows is professionally affiliated with the Association for Women in Architecture (AWA) and the Society for Nutrition Education (SNE). She holds a standard California teaching credential for Architecture and for Nutrition.
Scope and Content
The Dows collection consists of hand-drafted architectural drawings with supporting photographs, slides, and textual descriptions of California residential buildings renovated or expanded by Wena Dows from 1952 to 2005. In addition, there are plans for a few commercial projects with limited descriptive information. The textual descriptions contain Dows' handwritten notes on the client's requirements for the project, sketches of the existing building layout and dimensions, lists of the materials to be used for the project and specifications for some projects. Photographs of the building, before and after the work, accompany some of the project documents.
Arrangement
The collection has been arranged into a Project Index. which is a way to organize the various formats of architectural records from the same project. The index is arranged alphabetically by client name and contains information, where available, about the location, date, project type, architect, collaborators, and formats for each project in the collection.
A Summary of the Project Index. is listed below. Consult the Project Index. for location information.
Client Name/Project Title (location, date, architect/collaborator) [Format - Ms=Manuscripts, Dr=Drawings, Ph=Photograghs, S=Slides ]
Index Terms
Subjects:
International Archive of Women in Architecture (IAWA)
Genre and Form Terms:
Architectural drawings.
Occupations:
Architects.
Contents List
- Biographical information (Box-folder 1:15)
- Project Records (Map-case 35/Drawers 1-7)
  Arrangement
  A Summary of the Project Index. is listed below. Consult the Project Index. for location information.
  Client Name/Project Title (location, date, architect/collaborator) [Format - Ms=Manuscripts, Dr=Drawings, Ph=Photograghs, S=Slides ]
  - Drawing inventories (Box-folder 1:16)
  - Abrams, Judy ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-84; addition ) Collaborator: Tim Skilton, contractor [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Albertson, Marvin ( Beverly Hills; CA; Jul-85; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Alexander, Hanan and Shelley ( Los Angeles; CA; May-92; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Allen, Charles and Susan ( Los Angeles; CA; 1981; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Altman, Fred and Jamie ( Culver City; CA; May-84; addition [not built] ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Amit, Amos ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-86; addition over exisiting garage ) [ Dr ]
  - Amlani, Altaf ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-93; residence ) [ Dr ]
  - Anderson, Martin and Dorothy ( Los Angeles; CA; 1986; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Andonian, G.G. and Sonja ( Hollywood; CA; Aug-77; addition, remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Appleman, Michael and Irma ( Pacific Palisades; CA; Nov-89; deck addition, bath remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Ashe, Blanche ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-85; remodel ) Collaborator: Jim Marshall, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Atchley, Ron and Adele ( Santa Monica; CA; Mar-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Averseng, Rene ( Hollywood; CA; Dec-77; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Aylmer, David and Miriam ( Canoga Park; CA; Mar-83; family room addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Baltzer, Robert ( Los Angeles; CA; 1984; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Baltzer, Robert ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-80; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Balzac, Sheldon and Corinne ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Bambadji, Fred ( Encino; CA; Dec-97; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Banchoff, Dennis ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-98; bath remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Banchoff, Dennis ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-90; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Banchoff, Dennis ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-98; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Bass, Michael and Judy ( Pacific Palisades; CA; May-79; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Bear, Michael ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-88; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Beck, Melvin and Bella ( Studio City; CA; Apr-00; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Behling, Ron and Jackie ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-94; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Behling, Ron and Jackie ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-88; addition, remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Behling, Ron and Jackie ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-85; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Belinkoff, Alan ( Beverly Hills; CA; Feb-86; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Benda, Richard ( Pasadena; CA; Jul-84; addition ) Note: owner-built [ Dr ]
  - Benda, Richard ( Pasadena; CA; Jul-80; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Benson, Sidney ( Palos Verdes Estates; CA; Dec-76; garden walls ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Bergen, Dan and Karen ( Culver City; CA; Apr-93; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Berger, Jeanne ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-92; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Berger, Jeanne ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-89; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Bergman, Gregory and Leah ( Los Angeles; CA; May-81; 2nd story addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Berman, Ron ( Los Angeles; CA; 1978; dining addition, deck ) [ Dr ]
  - Bernard, David ( Santa Monica; CA; 1973; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Bernard, David ( Santa Monica; CA; 1971; remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Bernard, Phyllis [ Ms ]
  - Beydler, Gary and Sarah ( Los Angeles; CA; 1980; addition ) Collaborator: Tim Skilton, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Bilgrai, Benjamin ( Los Angeles; CA; 1980; family room addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Binder, Bernard and Bernice ( Culver City; CA; Dec-83; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Bjorklund, L.ois ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Blake, Bern and Donna ( Santa Monica; CA; Dec-93; garage remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Block, Alan and Jan ( Studio City; CA; Apr-82; addition [not built] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Blumenkranz, Harriet ( Santa Monica; CA; Sep-85; addition ) Collaborator: Herman Bros. Construction [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Boime, Albert and Myra ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Bowers, W. L. ( Palmer Lake; CO; Sep-54; cabin ) [ Dr ]
  - Bradmore Realty, Building 1 ( Valencia; CA; Dec-96; interior remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Brill, Bob ( Culver City; CA; Mar-79; remodeling, addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Brill, Bob ( Culver City; CA; Oct-75; second story addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Britt, Diana ( Pasadena; CA; Jul-98; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Brittingham, Marty ( Los Angeles; CA; May-83; greenhouse addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Brittingham, Marty ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-80; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Brockman, Seymore and Sylvia ( Beverly Hills; CA; Sep-91; master closet addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Broder, Melvin ( Encino; CA; Nov-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Broder, Melvin ( Encino; CA; Jul-89; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Broder, Melvin ( Encino; CA; Nov-88; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Brown, Joe ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-80; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Buerge Motor Car Company ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-95; interior remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Burger King ( Northridge; CA; Oct-76; drive-thru extension ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Caballero, James and Peggy ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-83; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Sl ]
  - Campbell, Jack and Filomina ( Santa Monico; CA; Jan-94; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Campbell, Jack and Filomina ( Santa Monica; CA; 1986; addtion ) [ Dr ]
  - Caren, Jeff and Adrea ( Beverly Hills; CA; 1978, 1980; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Carey, Glenn ( Chatsworth; CA; Aug-83; residence ) [ Dr ]
  - Carey, Harlan and Harriet ( Los Angeles; CA; 1978-1979; remodel [exterior only built] ) [ Ms, Dr, Sl ]
  - Caudill, Paulette ( El Segundo; CA; Aug-01; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Charwat, Andrew and Halima ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-01; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Chanon, Ed ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-89; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Chenoweth, M./J. Wilkins ( Redondo Beach; CA; Jun-05; addition ) Collaborator: Bill Morris, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Chlebowski, Rowan and Joan ( Rancho Palos Verdes; CA; Jul-92; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Chlebowski, Rowan and Joan ( Rancho Palos Verdes; CA; Apr-91; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Chlebowski, Rowan and Joan ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-80; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Chlowitz, Allan ( Marina del Ray; CA; ca. 1978; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Chock/Kelly ( Los Angeles; CA; May-98; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Cloud, Stan/Lynn Olson ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-84; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Coleman, Barry ( Long Beach; CA; Oct-87; addition, remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Colter, Gerry and Miriam ( Encino; CA; Jun-78; addition, remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Combs, Richard and Mary ( Woodland Hills; CA; Apr-80; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Cooper, Boyd and Susan ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-79; guest house ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Darnov, Morris and Natalie ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Apr-94; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Davidson, J. Leroy ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-67; remodeling, addition ) Collaborator: James Watt, builder [ Dr ]
  - Davis, Mary ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Dee, Jeremy and Joanne ( North Hollywood; CA; Jun-91; addition ) [ Dr, Ph ]
  - Denty, Robert ( Torrance; CA; May-88; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Deonier, Richard and Sylvia ( La Canada; CA; Mar-80; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Deutsch, Stanford ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-86; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Deutsch, Stephen and Shelley ( Studio City; CA; Mar-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Deutsch, Stephen and Shelley ( Studio City; CA; Apr-89; master bath/closet ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Deutsch, Stephen and Shelley ( Studio City; CA; Aug-81; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Dews, E. ( Santa Monica; CA;; garage in front [not built] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Dews, E. ( Santa Monica; CA; May-75; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - DiGregorio, Concezio and Roseanne ( Culver City; CA; 1983; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Ditlove, Jack and Trish ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-79; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Dones, Staurt/J. Siegel ( Studio City; CA; Apr-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Douglass, William ( Palos Verdes Estates; CA; Mar-88; deck ) [ Dr ]
  - Downes, Chloris/Sieglinde D. Keith ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Duban, Dennis ( Hollywood; CA; Mar-84; interior remodel ) Collaborator: Michael List Associates, Inerior designer [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Dunn, Arnold and Doris ( Pacific Palisades; CA; Jan-83; deck addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Dyer, Jim and Saren ( Malibu; CA; Aug-01; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Eisenstein, Robert ( Beverly Hills; CA; Feb-88; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Fair, Stephen and Janet ( Van Nuys; CA; Feb-81; addition ) Collaborator: Ron Whitlock, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Fee, Harold and Dorothy ( Torrance; CA; Jul-99; residence, apartment ) [ Dr ]
  - Feedman, Abe ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-78; kitchen remodel [not built] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Feigenson, Emily/Dennis Purless ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-95; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Fein, Alan and Lucy ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-05; sunroom, deck addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Fein, Alan and Lucy ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-04; storage room ) [ Dr ]
  - Fein, Alan and Lucy ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-01; porch enclosure ) [ Dr ]
  - Fein, Alan and Lucy ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-98; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Fenigstein, Jack ( Los Angeles; CA; November 1986, December 1988; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Feuer, Michael and Gail ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-97; remodel, plans for study 2 ) [ Dr ]
  - Fox, James and Judy ( Studio City; CA; Jun-98; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Fox, Robert and Isabelle ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Dec-99; kitchen counters, splash plan ) [ Dr ]
  - Fox, Robert and Isabelle ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Aug-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Fox, Robert and Isabelle ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Dec-95; shop remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Fox, Robert and Isabelle ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Feb-93; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Frankos, K.J. ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-78; bedroom addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Freed, Patricia and Donald ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-01; master suite remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Freed, Patricia and Donald ( Los Angeles; CA; May -October 2000; bay addition, kitchen remodel, fence ) [ Dr ]
  - Freed, Patricia and Donald ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-98; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Frelinger, David ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-93; kitchen ) [ Dr ]
  - Frelinger, David ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-89; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Frisch, David ( Los Angeles; CA; 1980; dining room extension ) [ Dr ]
  - Frisch, David ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Gansky, Paul ( Culver City; CA; Jan-84; desk enclosure ) [ Dr ]
  - Gansky, Paul ( Culver City; CA; May-83; 2nd story addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Garber, Lance/Laurie Bickove ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-90; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Garcia, John ( Los Angeles; CA; 197?; addition [not built?] ) [ Dr ]
  - Gardner, Stuart(Huntington Beach; CA; 1985; residence ) [ Dr ]
  - Gass, James and Sharon ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Gelfand, Gilbert and Candance ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-99; addition, remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Gilad, Oded and Ilana ( Los Angeles; CA; May-93; cabinets ) [ Dr ]
  - Gilbert, Gilbert and Helen ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Dec-99; television cabinet ) [ Dr ]
  - Gilbert, Gilbert and Helen ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Apr-97; landscaping plan ) [ Dr ]
  - Gilbert, Gilbert and Helen ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Mar-96; revisions ) [ Dr ]
  - Gilbert, Gilbert and Helen ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Aug-95; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Giorgianni, Joe and Betty ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-77; study alterations ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Glass/Sette ( Los Angeles; CA; 197?; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Goetz, Matthew and Marjorie ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-92; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Goldfried, Bob and Rosalie ( Encino; CA; Mar-98; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Goldfried, Bob and Rosalie ( Encino; CA; Jul-92; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Goldstein, Don and Toni ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-80; addition ) Collaborator: Arne Pearson, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Goldstein, Don and Toni ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-80; addition [not built] ) [ Dr ]
  - Goldstein, Jon and Margy ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-80; addition [not built?] ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Goodman, Michael and Claudine ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-91; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Goodman, Michael and Claudine ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-86; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Gordon, Len and Judee ( Woodland Hills; CA; Nov-82; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Gordon, Marty ( Beverly Hills; CA; Nov-87; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Grant, Jeffrey and Joanne ( Los Angeles; CA; 1978, 1984; remodel ) Collaborator: Richard Flinn, contractor, both times [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Graves, John and Fran ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-79; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Greenspan, Robb ( Encino; CA; Jun-93; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Greif, Ellen ( Culver City; CA; Feb-96; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Gryczman, Bluma and Max ( Encino; CA; Jul-96; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Gryczman, Steve and Sue ( Tarzana; CA; Jun-92; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Gutierrez, Walter ( North Hollywood; CA; Oct-86; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Gutman, Steven and Dee ( Woodland Hills; CA; Feb-00; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Hacker, Rick and Joan ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Jun-05; addition ) Collaborator: Ron Whitlock, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Hansen, Tammy ( Torrance; CA; Mar-99; addition, kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Hanson A./T. Kafka ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-97; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Hanson A./T. Kafka ( Culver City; CA; Sep-93; addition, remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Harris, Harry E. and MaryAnn ( Pacific Palisades; CA; May-78; kitchen remodel ) Collaborator: John Thompson, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Heldman, Morris/L. Gollub ( Culver City; CA; Apr-90; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Helperin, Sandy ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-95; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Herby's Self Service Drive In ( Oakland; CA; Aug-52; ) [ Dr ]
  - Hargitay, Mickey and Ellen ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Herring, Monte and Maureen ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-93; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Hirsch, Joel and Hanita ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-94; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Hirsch, Warner and Jane ( Los Angeles; CA; 1984; cabinets ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Hirsch, Warner and Jane ( Los Angeles; CA; 1984; cabinets ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Holstein, Burt and Pat ( Studio City; CA; Dec-90; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Hopkins, Jack and Elaine ( Venice; CA; Jul-80; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Hull, Edna ( Culver City; CA; Apr-93; slope stabilization ) [ Dr ]
  - Hunnicutt, Gerald and DeeDee ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-80; second floor addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Hunt, Marianne ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-84; addition ) Collaborator: Tim Skilton, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Hunt, Marianne ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-84; addition ) Collaborator: Tim Skilton, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Ilves, Dan and Peggy ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-00; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Iversen, Richard and Myra ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-80; garage addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Izumi, Tak ( Los Angeles; CA; Jun-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - J-D Industries ( Los Angeles; CA; May-83; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Jacobs, Lucien and Susan ( Woodland Hills; CA; Oct-93; addition/remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Jackson, Murray ( Sherman Oaks; CA; Jun-88; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Jameson, Don and June ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-95; earthquake remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Jameson, Don and June ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-93; interior remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Jobe, R. and Kay ( Manhattan Beach; CA; Jun-98; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Johnson, M.K. and Virginia ( Culver City; CA; Jun-98; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Johnson, R. ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-78; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Jones, Camille ( Culver City; CA; Aug-82; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Kahan, Stan and Sandy ( Beverly Hills; CA; May-91; kitchen plan ) [ Dr ]
  - Kanegsberg, Edward ( Pacific Palisades; CA; Jun-81; 2 story addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Kaniger, Ed and Delores ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-93; family room cabinets ) [ Dr ]
  - Kaplan, Stephen and Lisa ( Sherman Oaks; CA; May-83; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Kawamura, Roy ( Northridge; CA; Apr-80; room addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Kehr, Robert ( Los Angeles; CA; May-89; addition, kitchen remodel ) [ Dr, Ph ]
  - Kehr, Robert ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-81; den extension ) [ Dr ]
  - Kelly, Dennis and Bonnie ( Santa Monica; CA; Sep-94; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Kemp, Charles ( Inglewood; CA; Aug-76; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Kennerly, Martin and Dorice ( Santa Monica; CA; May-98; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Kibota, Scott and Dolly ( Redondo Beach; CA; Apr-02; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - King, Ernest ( Los Angeles; CA; 197?; addition [not built?] ) [ Dr ]
  - Kissane, Ruth/Joan Karpe ( Venice; CA; May-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Kitano, Gerald and Jane ( Culver City; CA; Apr-90; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Klinger, R. ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-66; addition ) [ Dr, Ph ]
  - Kodimer, Charles and Jenny ( Los Angeles; CA; 1986; addition ) Collaborator: P&L Construction, builders [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Kolb, Marvin and Karen ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-88; bath remodeling ) [ Dr ]
  - Kolb, Marvin and Karen ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-79; kitchen remodeling ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Korn, Barry and Helene ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-79; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Kort, Steven and Marla ( Tarzana; CA; Apr-92; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Krakow, E. ( Los Angeles; CA; Jul-88; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Kushel, Barbara ( Los Angeles; CA; Nov-77; kitchen remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Kvitky, Joel ( Los Angeles; CA; Sep-79; remodel and garage ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Kvitky, Martin and Sylvia ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-85; remodel ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Landerer, Sheldon and April ( Van Nuys; CA; Jun-77; second story addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Latter, Carole and Rick ( Los Angeles; CA; Dec-91; addition ) [ Ms, Dr, Ph ]
  - Latter, Carole and Rick ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-85; addition ) Collaborator: Herman Bros. Construction [ Dr ]
  - Lebovitz, Joel ( Tarzana; CA; Nov-89; addition + revisions ) [ Dr ]
  - Lee, David ( Santa Monico; CA; Mar-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Levin, Ron and Coral ( Los Angeles; CA; May-91; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Levy, Gabriel and Lilly ( Beverly Hills; CA; Mar-81; kitchen addition ) Collaborator: RGA contactor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Levy, Jonathan and Doris ( Culver City; CA; Jan-01; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Limberg, Ed and Kelly ( Rancho Palos Verdes; CA; Aug-01; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - List, Michael ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-89; addition ) [ Dr, Ph ]
  - Lock, Doug and Donna ( Manhattan Beach; CA; Jun-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Loman, Hal and Barbara ( Sepulveda; CA; Oct-81; remodel ) Collaborator: RGA, builders [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Lopez, Ruben and Felicia ( Pacific Palisades; CA; Feb-82; addition ) Collaborator: Don Johnson, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Los Feliz Towers Exercise Facility ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-97; exercise sauna and bath ) [ Dr ]
  - Loschen, Leslie and Jane ( Rolling Hills Estate; CA; Jun-91; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Lukas, Henry V. ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-81; bath remodels ) Note: owner contracted [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Lukas, Henry V. ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-76; kitchen remodel ) Note: owner contracted [ Dr ]
  - Madison, Charles ( Los Angeles; CA; Jan-78; garage and remodel [not built??] ) [ Dr ]
  - Malamud, Gerald and Patricia ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-96; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Markell, Jon and Cari ( Los Angeles; CA; Aug-94; remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Marker, David ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-88; kitchen/master bath remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Martin, Darlene ( Long Beach; CA; May-02; addition, remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Martinez, Ralph/Judy Delafield ( Solvang; CA; Aug-01; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Mason, Barry ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-89; revisions to addition ) [ Dr ]
  - McCalla, Carl and Judy ( Studio City; CA; Oct-93; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Medway, Jerald and Ellen ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-00; 2nd floor addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Medway, Jerald and Ellen ( Los Angeles; CA; May-99; master bath/closet remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Medway, Jerald and Ellen ( Los Angeles; CA; Apr-96; kitchen remodel ) [ Dr ]
  - Medway, Jerald and Ellen ( Los Angeles; CA; Feb-85; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Merifield, Paul and Ruth ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-78; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Merritt, Sharyne/Gene Miller ( Montecito; CA; Apr-96; remodel to guest house ) [ Dr ]
  - Miller, Steve and Andrea ( Manhattan Beach; CA; Dec-99; addition ) [ Dr ]
  - Millman, Michael ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-83; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Milstein, Hymie and Amy ( Los Angeles; CA; Oct-84; decks, remodel ) Collaborator: Thomas Edwards, contractor [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Mitchell, Ken and Dorothy ( Malibu; CA; May-78; residence ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Mizrahi, Cesar and Esther ( Los Angeles; CA; May-85; addition ) [ Ms, Dr ]
  - Molinari, Del and Diane ( Los Angeles; CA; Mar-75; remodeling plan ) [ Ms, Dr ]